One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Hey! Quit slackin' off!
Hey! Bırak aylaklığı!
Okay.
Tamam.
Hey, cabin boys! After sweeping, wash the windows!
Yerleri süpürdükten sonra camları da silin!
Yes, sir!
Başüstüne!
– One! Two! Three! Four!
– Bir! İki! Üç! Dört!
I can't stand this. Forget Koby— why do I have to be a cabin boy?!
Dayanamıyorum artık, Koby'i bırak da ben neden kamarot oldum ki?!
Dammit! I only ended up here because of that Straw Hat!
Kahretsin! Hep o Hasır Şapka'nın suçu!
It's all his fault!
Hep onun yüzünden!
It's all because of Straw Hat that I'm stuck doing this crap!
Onun yüzünden bu boktan işe bulaştım!
Helmeppo.
Helmeppo-san.
What do you want?! Don't act like we're friends!
Ne istiyorsun be?! Arkadaşmışız gibi davranma.
Nothing good comes from blaming Luffy for everything that happens.
Olanlar için Luffy-san'ı suçlamanın bir manası yok.
For a long time, you lived protected by your father's influence.
Yıllardır babanın torpiliyle yaşıyordun.
But from now on, we need to face forward and seek our own dreams!
Artık önümüze bakıp kendi hayallerimizin peşinden koşma zamanı.
What are you...?
Ne diyorsun...?
I have a dream.
Bir hayalim var.
Someday, I will be a Marine officer who cracks down on bad guys!
Bir gün, suçlulara aman vermeyen bir Donanma subayı olacağım!
What are you going on about?!
Ne masal okuyorsun lan?!
A wimp like you becoming an officer for the Marines?!
Senin gibi bir süt bebesi Donanma subayı olacak, ha?
Quit dreaming!
Hayal kurmayı kes!
I will do it!
Olacağım!
I decided on it after seeing how Luffy lives his life!
Luffy-san'ın yaşam tarzını gördüm ve kararımı verdim.
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!
Ben, Korsanlar Kralı olmaya karar verdim.
This is what I've decided, so if I die, then fine by me!
Bu yolda ölsem bile farketmez.
So just like Luffy, I've made up my mind to risk everything
Ben de Luffy-san gibi her şeyimi riske atarak hedefimin peşinden gideceğim.
You see? So let's work hard together!
Anladın mı? O yüzden birlikte sıkı çalışalım!
Screw you!
Kes lan!
How dare you lecture me?!
Sen kimsin bana nasihat veriyorsun?!
Just when did you get so full of yourself?!
İki günde adam mı oldun?!
What could you possibly learn from that despicable Straw Hat?!
O aşağılık Hasır Şapka'dan ne hayat dersi alabilirsin ki?!
Don't insult Luffy!
Luffy-san'a hakaret etmeyi kes!
I haven't said anything wrong!
Ben, yanlış bir şey söylemedim!
Wrong or not, you still piss me off!
Doğru ya da değil, yine de sana gıcık oluyorum!
Helmeppo! Please! You have to be realistic.
Helmeppo-san! Lütfen! Uyan artık.
Look who's talking!
Diyene bak!
Take this!
Al ulan!
Get ahold of yourself!
Kendine gel!
Huh? What's going on?!
Ha? Ne oluyor?!
– W-We're sorry! – We're sorry!
– Ö-Özür dileriz! – Özür dileriz!
Really? The explosion earlier was because of you?
Cidden, deminki patlama sizin yüzünüzden miydi?
So then they kicked you out of the Marines?
Sizi donanmadan attılar mı peki?
Thank you.
Elinize sağlık.
No, we managed to avoid being discharged.
Hayır, bir şekilde kovulmaktan kurtulduk.
But now we're under a fifty-year contract with no pay.
Ama şimdi, 50 sene ücretsiz çalışmak zorundayız.
Getting canned would've been a mercy.
Kovulmaktan beter.
Attention!
Dikkat!
I will now fill you in on our current mission!
Şimdi, görevimiz ile ilgili bilgilendirme yapacağım!
– Hey! – What do you want?!
– Hey! – Ne istiyorsun?
D-Daddy...
B-Baba...
Morgan, a former Marine captain, is to be sent to headquarters
Eski Donanma Albayı Morgan, ana karargâha götürülecek.
to face a court-martial for the crimes of military exploitation and civilian torment!
Orada yetki suistimali ve sivillere zarar vermekten yargılanacak.
Today's mission is his transfer and delivery to Vice Admiral Garp!
Bugünkü görevimiz, onu Koramiral Garp'a teslim etmek!
I am Captain "Axe-Hand" Morgan of the Marines!
Ben, Donanma Albayı "Balta-El" Morgan'ım!
Scum without rank or status should kneel before me!
Rütbesiz ayak takımı bana kafa tutamaz!
This was the only outcome, wasn't it?
Başka bir yolu yok değil mi?
I'm not denying that he should be court-martialed or whatever.
Askeri mahkemede yargılanmasın demiyorum da...
He deserves what's coming to him, after all.
Ektiğini biçiyor sonuçta...
But even so, I used to respect him.
Her şeye rağmen yine de ona saygı duyardım!
Damn it!
Kahretsin!
Why?!
Neden?!
Tell me, do you think they'll execute him?
Sence onu idam mı edecekler?
Th-That's...
Şey...
There's probably no getting around that either, huh?
Kaçarı yok herhalde, değil mi?
That's just how Daddy is.
Babam böyledir işte.
Helmeppo...
Helmeppo-san...
All hands on deck!
Herkes görevinin başına!
Fall in!
Hizaya girin!
– It's Vice Admiral Garp! – It's Garp the Fist!
– Koramiral Garp geliyor! – Yumruk Garp!
So that's Marine Headquarters' Vice Admiral Garp the Fist!
Demek Donanma'nın Yumruk Garp'ı o!
Traveling all over the Grand Line, he's the hero of the seas!
Grand Line'ın dört bir yanına hakim, denizlerin kahramanı!
Vice Admiral Garp, thank you for personally coming all this way!
Koramiral Garp, bunca yolu geldiğiniz için teşekkürler!
We hereby deliver to you Morgan!
Morgan'ı size teslim ediyoruz!
Stop, Helmeppo!
Dur, Helmeppo-san!
Umm... Vice Admiral Garp?
Eee... Koramiral Garp?
Vice Admiral Garp!
Koramiral Garp!
Quiet!
Sessizlik!
I hear you.
Seni duyabiliyorum.
I've been up for five days now.
Beş gündür uyumuyorum.
Thank you for your hard work, sir!
Sağ olun efendim, her şey için.
It's no big deal since I'm trying for a new doughnut-eating record.
Yeni bir donut yeme rekoru denediğim için bu pek önemli değil.
Sir?
Efendim?
But a lack of rest and sleep is getting to me after the 842nd one.
842. donuttan sonra uykusuzluk vurmaya başladı.
Old man, cut the sleeping act.
İhtiyar, uyuyor numarasını bırak.
Everybody freeze!
Kimse kımıldamasın!
Move and I'll hack up this cabin boy and feed him to the sharks!
Kıpırdayan olursa bu kamarotu parçalar, köpek balıklarına yem ederim!
D-Daddy!
B-Baba!
Please stop!
Dur, lütfen!
Helmeppo's your own son, isn't he?!
Helmeppo-san, senin öz oğlun değil mi?
Son?! I don't need such a thing!
Oğlum mu?! Kim ne yapsın onu be!
What I want is freedom!
Ben özgürlüğümü istiyorum!
I'll smash him to a bloody pulp if need be!
Bunun için de kim olursa olsun gözden çıkarmaya hazırım!
D-Daddy...
B-Baba...
H-Help me!
İ-İmdat!
So long, suckers!
Hoşça kalın, kerizler!
Helmeppo!
Helmeppo-san!
Ready the cannon!
Topu hazırlayın!
Load! Aim!
Doldur! Nişan al!
Target: 16 degrees starboard.
Hedef, 16 derece sancak yönünde!
Distance: eight, two, six, three. Ready!
Mesafe: sekiz, iki, altı, üç. Hazır!
P-P-Please wait!
L-L-Lütfen bekleyin!
That's dangerous!
Bu çok tehlikeli!
– What are you doing?! – Get down from there!
– Napıyorsun?! – İn oradan aşağı!
P-Please don't shoot! My friend...
L-Lütfen ateş etmeyin! Arkadaşım...
My friend's onboard!
Arkadaşım da orada!
Move.
Çekil.
No!
Hayır!
Then I'll cut you down!
O zaman ben indirmesini bilirim.
That's much better than just abandoning my friend!
Arkadaşım hayatı için ölümü tercih ederim!
Please! I'll go capture him myself!
Lütfen! Onu gidip kendim yakalayacağım!
Come back, you idiot!
Aptal, gel buraya!
There's no way you can capture him!
Onu yakalamanın imkanı yok!
Just let him go.
Bırak gitsin.
He's either a complete lunatic, or...
Ya delinin teki, ya da...
What do we do?!
Ne yapacağız?!
What's with all the racket? I'm finally awake.
Nedir bu tantana? Sonunda kendime geldim.
Vice Admiral Garp, we thought you were a goner!
Koramiral Garp, işiniz bitti sanmıştım!
Huh?! Who's a goner?!
Ha?! Kimin işi bitti?
I missed it because I was asleep! Where's the victim?!
Uyuyordum diye kaçırdım! Kim yaralandı?!
Me?
Ben mi?
I'm free!
Özgürüm!
Just you watch! The world will kneel before me once again!
Bak gör! Dünya bir kez daha önümde diz çökecek!
Today, I begin a new life as the ruler of the Morgan Kingdom!
Bugün Morgan Krallığı'nın ilk günüdür!
Now! Set our course west!
Şimdi, rotamızı batıya çevir!
What are you doing?! I said to set course due west!
Napıyorsun?! Rotayı batıya çevir dedim!
No!
Hayır!
I'll have no part in this!
Bunlar beni ilgilendirmiyor!
Despite what happened, he still covered for us!
Bütün olanlara rağmen beni korudu!
Even when getting sacked by the Marines would end his dream!
Bunun, hayallerine mal olacağını bilmesine rağmen!
After all that, he's still protecting me! I can do it, too!
Her şeye rağmen hâlâ beni koruyor! O hâlde ben de yapabilirim.
I'm going to capture you, Dad! Just give up–
Baba, seni geri götüreceğim! Sakın direnm–
Are you dim?! Who do you think you're talking to, huh?!
Aptal mısın sen? Kimle konuştuğunu sanıyorsun, ha?
What can useless scum like you do to me?!
Senin gibi işe yaramaz bir sümsük bana ne yapabilir ki?
Dammit!
Lanet olsun!
Know your place, you pathetic insect!
Seni zavallı böcek, haddini bil!
As if I'd ever listen to you!
Lafların bana sökmez!
I'm the one who decides how I'll live!
Nasıl yaşacayacağıma kendim karar veririm!
Quit getting the wrong idea! What can a piece of scum like you do?!
Boş hayallere kapılma! Ne yapabileceğini sanıyorsun ki, ezik?!
He isn't alone!
Ben de varım!
You!
Sen!
Morgan!
Morgan!
Pathetic! Pathetic! Pathetic!
İçler acısı! Yazık! Yazık!
So what if a couple of insects are swarming together?!
Birkaç böcek toplaşıp bir olmuşsa ne değişecek?!
Get in my way, and I'll end you both in one fell swoop!
Yoluma çıkarsanız ikinizi de ikiye bölerim!
I'm sorry you got dragged into this when you tried to save me.
Seni de bu duruma sürüklediğim için üzgünüm.
What are you talking about?
Ne diyorsun sen?
Aren't we friends?
Biz arkadaş değil miyiz?
Koby...
Koby...
You damn insects aren't even worth killing.
Siz böcekler, öldürmeye bile değmezsiniz.
Never show yourselves to me again!
Bir daha yoluma çıkmayın!
Morgan!
Morgan!
I'll let you go for today,
Bugün gitmene müsade ediyorum,
but someday I will surpass you!
ama bir gün, yine karşılaşacağız!
Someday, I will catch you!
Bir gün, seni yakalayacağım!
Just you wait!
Bekle ve gör!
Please forgive my poor supervision!
Lütfen berbat gözetimimi affedin!
Letting him flee is the biggest blunder in my life!
Mahkumun kaçmasına izin vermek hayatımın hatasıydı!
We're very sorry, sir!
Çok özür dileriz, efendim!
These two are now forever barred from military service!
Bu olanlardan sonra bu ikisi Donanma'dan şutlanacaktır!
You two truly are lost causes.
Tam anlamıyla ümitsiz vakasınız.
I doubt anyone anywhere would take you in now.
Bu saatten sonra sizi kim ne yapsın.
And if we turn you loose, you'd be a nuisance to all.
Sizi atsak gider başkalarına bela olursunuz.
You leave me no choice. Come with me to Marine Headquarters!
Başka çare bırakmadınız. Benimle karargâha geliyorsunuz!
Vice Admiral! You're taking them with you to Marine Headquarters?!
Koramiral! Onları karargâha mı götüreceksiniz?!
Am I not allowed?
Olmaz mı?
No, do as you please.
O-Olur, siz daha iyi bilirsiniz.
Any objections, you two?
Sizin bir itirazınız var mı?
If you want to run away, now's your chance.
Kaçmak istiyorsanız, tam zamanı,
Though I have no intention of letting you say no.
ama ben de peşinize düşerim, ona göre!
My, oh my, what an odd day this has been!
Vay anasını, ne garip bir gün oluyor!
What?! Marine Headquarters?!
Ne?! Donanma Karargâhı mı?!
Yeah. Vice Admiral Garp seems to be as eccentric as people say.
Evet, Koramiral Garp, dedikleri gibi garip biriymiş.
But doesn't he have an exceptional reputation?
Ama namı büyük biridir, değil mi?
Yeah, you have no idea.
Evet, hem de ne büyük.
Then those two must show a lot of promise.
O zaman o ikisinde bir ışık görmüş olmalı.
Hm?
Ha?
Stupid! Stupid! Stupid! Stupid! Stupid!
Aptal! Aptal! Aptal! Aptal! Aptal!
Why did you let them go without saying anything?!
Neden hiçbir şey demeden gitmelerine izin verdiniz?!
Stupid! Stupid! Stupid! Stupid! Stupid!
Aptal! Aptal! Aptal! Aptal! Aptal!
I... wanted to play with them more.
Onlarla daha çok oynamak istiyordum.
I wanted to talk to them more.
Daha çok sohbet etmek istiyordum.
I was learning how to cook so I could make them tasty lunch boxes!
Onlara güzel yemekler yapabilmek için aşçılık öğreniyordum!
I didn't even get to say goodbye!
Onlarla vedalaşamadım bile!
Ah... Um...
Ah... Şey...
Why did they leave?!
Neden gittiler?!
Ah, I'm sorry! Forgive me!
Ahh, üzgünüm! Bağışla beni!
Rika, that's enough. Leave him alone.
Rika, bu kadar yeter. Rahat bırak adamı.
Don't worry. They'll surely be back... once they become fine officers.
Üzülme, geri döneceklerdir. Hem de çok iyi subaylar olarak.
But at any rate,
Böyle işler yaparak...
can we really become Marines by doing things like this?
gerçekten donanma subayı olabilir miyiz?
This might be that old dog's hobby, you know.
Bu, o yaşlı bunağın hobisi olmasın?
Hobby?
Hobi mi?
Yup. It's called "the retired geezer's torment of youths."
Evet. "Emekli bunağın gençlere işkence hobisi".
Don't you think he's shifty and strange enough for that?
Olamaz mı? Garip ve sakat bir tipti.
Shut up, birds!
Ötmeyi kesin, kuşlar!
Marine Branch 153 Shells Town, East Blue
153. Donanma Birliği Shells Kasabası, Doğu Mavi
"Cabin Boy"
"Kamarot"
Vice Admiral Garp Marine Headquarters
Koramiral Garp Donanma Karargâhı
"Justice"
"Adalet"
"The Marines"
"Donanma"